

CONTACT

Phone: 0838 7398 2044

Email: andritanuww@gmail.com

Address: Bogor, West Java

SOCIAL

Instagram; andritanuww

Github: Andritanu

Linkedin : Andriansah Tanuwijaya

SKILLS

HTML & CSS

PHP

MySqI

Sql server

Javascript (Basic)

GIT

Photoshop

Microsoft Office

English (Intermediate)

Laravel Framework

Bootstrap

Zend Framework

ANDRIANSAH TANUWIJAYA

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

SUMMARY

I am a software developer, especially in web development. I can work under pressure and in groups. I am a person who is happy and easy to socialize with, and I even work with people I just met. I have many years of experience in the field of software development.

WORK EXPERIENCE

CV IDS

Internship as Software developer | Sep 2020 - Dec 2020.

- Designed and created Student data Apps with Laravel Framework.
- Managed Teamwork using gitlab version control system.
- Visualized the user interface of the application using Figma.
- Managed Databases using PostgreSQL.
- Managed Teamwork using Trello as Project management tools.
- Learn representational state transfer (API).
- Contribute to develop Boarding School system Apps.

PT Square Gate One

PHP Programmer | Sep 2021 - Present.

- Develop, testing, and support FSCM Apps using Zend Framework.
- Preparing FSCM Apps for presentation to clients.
- Contributes Testing Apps with Quality assurance.
- Assist Quality assurance for SIT and UAT.
- Contributes Deployment Apps with System Administration.
- Fixed Bug's in FSCM Apps.
- Contributes to develop Smart Pemda Apps

EDUCATION

Wikrama 1 Garut Vocational Highschool

Computer Programming | 2018-2021.

Learn and explore how to develop software. Starting from making websites, applications, games and everything related to programming